close drawer
zopen drawer
pickup tupperware
close drawer
open tupperware
put tupperware and lid
pickup pan
move pasta from pan to tupperware using wooden spoon
still moving pasta
put pan and wooden spoon in sink
open tap
pickup lid
close tupperware
close tap
put tupperware
pick tupperware
open fridge
put tupperware
close fridge
open drawer
get jar
close drawer
open jar
put jar
pickup mesh strainer
put broccoli in jar
put strainer
hold and press and close jar
pickup jar
shake jar
open fridge
put jar
close fridge
pickup towel
pickup apron
put towel
wear apron
tie apron
pickup glasses
open cupboard
put glasses
pickup glasses
pickup mug
pickup plate
pickup plates
pickup cutlery
close drawer
open drawer
put cutlery
close drawer
wear gloves
pickup sponge
open tap
squeeze sponge
put liquid
wash wooden spoon
pickup knife
wash knife
pickup spoon
wash spoon
open tap
rinse spoon
put spoon
rinse knife
put knife
rinse wooden spoon
close tap
put spoon
pickup pan
wash pan
still washing pan
put sponge
open tap
rinse pan
still rinsing pan
close tap
open tap
rinse pan
close tap
put pan in drainer
pickup chopping board
wash chopping board
put sponge
open tap
rinse chopping board
close tap
put chopping board
pickup mesh strainer
wash mesh strainer
put sponge
open tap
rinse mesh strainer
close tap
put strainer in drainer
puckup pot
wash pot
open tap
rinse pot
close tap
put pot
pickup plate
wash plate
put sponge
open tap
rinse plate
close tap
put plate
pickup plate
open trash bin
close trash bin
wash plate
put sponge
open tap
rinse plate
close tap
put plate
open tupperware
pickup sponge
wash tupperware
put sponge
open tap
rinse tupperware
wash tupperware
put sponge
open tap
rinse tupperware
close tap
put tupperware
pickup lid
wash lid
open tap
rinse tupperware
close tap
pickup plate
wash plate
put sponge
open tap
rinse plate
close tap
put plate
pickup strainer
wash strainer
put sponge
open tap
rinse strainer
close tap
put strainer
empty sink
still emptying the water in the sink
pickup spoon
wash spoon
put sponge
open tap
rinse spoon
close tap
put spoon
empty sink
remove gloves
pickup water filter
pickup glass
drink from glass
put glass
remove apron
put apron
[END SUBTITLE]